l love Strawberry Quik.
It's my favorite pink fluid...
...uh, narrowly beating out Pepto-Bismol.
(Amy:)Oh, I know. I think it will go nicely
with what I have prepared for dinner.
(Sheldon:)Spaghetti with little pieces
of hot dog cut up in it.
- Just like your mommy used to make.
- Oh.
(Sheldon:)Yummy, yummy.
Yeah, we should do this more often.
(Sheldon:)Uh-oh.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, I did. I crossed a line.
l didn't mean to!
Who says that
right in the middle of sex?
l don't know. It just came out.
(Leonard:)People say weird things
during sex all the time.
(Penny:)- Well, they sure as hell don't say that.
- It was the heat of the moment.
(Penny:)No, the heat of the moment is,
"Yeah, just like that"...
...not, "Will you marry me?"
- I'm sorry, just give me another chance.
- So you can crawl under covers and go: